<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dhiraj Balakrishnan</title>
    <link>https://dhirajbalakrishnan.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dhiraj Balakrishnan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Theme - Potato Dark</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dhirajbalakrishnan.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>IPL Analytics</title>
      <link>https://dhirajbalakrishnan.dev/projects/ipl-analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 17:00:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dhirajbalakrishnan.dev/projects/ipl-analytics/</guid>
      <description>Overview We&amp;rsquo;ve all been engulfed by an uncertainity that is COVID-19 which doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to be going anywhere anytime soon. Of all the stuff that has come to an indefinite standstill, sporting action, especially cricket is something that we are missing the most.
It is now that time of the year where we would ideally be getting out of a hangover from the IPL. I have been an avid follower of the Indian Premier League from its inception, so much so that I wanted to fill in this void of having no IPL by looking at some of its data points and this exercise led me to build a side project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Leadership Lessons from my Personal Experience</title>
      <link>https://dhirajbalakrishnan.dev/posts/5-leadership-lessons-from-my-personal-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2020 18:50:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dhirajbalakrishnan.dev/posts/5-leadership-lessons-from-my-personal-experience/</guid>
      <description>It is not the genius at the top giving directions that makes people great. It is great people that make the guy at the top look like a genius.
 Before I start, I want to let you know that I am no expert in Leadership. I got an opportunity to lead a committee at Dell and I loved that experience. I am documenting the impact that it had on my life and the lessons that I have learnt from it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perfection is Overrated</title>
      <link>https://dhirajbalakrishnan.dev/posts/perfection-is-overrated/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 21:37:25 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dhirajbalakrishnan.dev/posts/perfection-is-overrated/</guid>
      <description>Practice makes Perfect
 I have a confession to make, I have been writing and re-writing this post for over two months now. During this interim, the blog&amp;rsquo;s title has changed thrice and the blog content has changed so much that the initial draft is nowhere close to this post. Having said this, you might be wondering why, and I don&amp;rsquo;t blame you for it. After all, this has been a real pain point for me and at one point I thought this is impossible for me to accomplish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impossible List</title>
      <link>https://dhirajbalakrishnan.dev/impossible-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dhirajbalakrishnan.dev/impossible-list/</guid>
      <description>We all die. The goal isn&amp;rsquo;t to live forever, the goal is to create something that will.
 For all of you who are wondering what an impossible list is, let me borrow a few sentences from Thomas Frank who was my inspiration for creating my own Impossible list.
 The impossible list is an ever-evolving list of experiences that build upon each other, help others as well as yourself, and implore you to take action.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>